Purple Hearts is a romance, drama film directed by Elizabeth Allen Rosenbaum.
An aspiring musician agrees to a marriage of convenience with a soon-to-deploy
Marine, but a tragedy soon turns their fake relationship all too real.
Cassie Salazar, played by Sofia Carson.
Luke Marrow, played by Nicholas Galitzine.
Toby, played by John Harlan Kim.
Frankie, played by Chosen Jacobs.
Johnno, played by Anthony Ippolito.
Jacob Marrow, played by Linden Ashby.
Purple Hearts is a 2022 American romantic drama film created for
Netflix and directed by Elizabeth Allen Rosenbaum.
It is based upon the novel of the same name by Tess Wakefield.
It stars Sofia Carson and Nicholas Galitzine.
The film was released on Netflix on July 29, 2022.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
The tone is emotional.